Guide to the Whitman College Fencing Club records 1995-2017, undated
Whitman College and Northwest Archives
Whitman College Fencing Club records
1995-2017, undated
Whitman College and Northwest Archives 345 Boyer Avenue Walla Walla, WA 99362 Archives@whitman.edu https://library.whitman.edu/archives/
Whitman College Fencing Club
WCA143
1.5 linear feet 1 box
This collection contains materials from the Whitman College Fencing Club.
Collection is open for research.
The Whitman College Fencing Club is one of the oldest active student groups on campus. The Whitman Fencing Team was formed in the 1940s, and in 2007 the name was changed to the Whitman College Fencing Club. As a club, the organization focuses on helping members improve their technique and explore different types of armed combat.
Materials in the Whitman College Fencing Club records include rank tests, certificates, member notes and posters.
Whitman College Fencing Club
Whitman College--Students--Societies, etc.; Whitman College--Sports
Colleges and Universities
- Awards, 1995, 2014-2016 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Constitution and bylaws, 2012-2016 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, January 5, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Finance handbook, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Financial records, 2010-2017 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Fliers, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Glossary, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Noble Science of Defense workshop, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Rank test score sheets: First, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Rank test score sheets: Second, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
- Rank test score sheets: Third, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Rank test score sheets: Fourth, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)